
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>General &#8211; googlecoincrypto</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Your homepage for CryptoCurrency Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 17:56:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/cropped-art-background-bitcoin-1263324-2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>General &#8211; googlecoincrypto</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is cryptocurrency? Get rich with cryptocurrencies.</title>
		<link>/cryptocurrencies-information-page/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 17:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[waterbyte]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryto-introduction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crytocurrency]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin, Ripple, Ethereum and countless others. There are more than 1600+ cryptocurrencies currently. It is hard to believe that 10 years ago they didn&#8217;t even exist. Yet in 10 years, they have reached staggering heights in terms of value. What are these new type of currencies? How is it going to affect us? Will I&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptocurrencies-information-page/">What is cryptocurrency? Get rich with cryptocurrencies.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="">googlecoincrypto</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-6 aligncenter" title="crypto coin" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/bitcoin-blockchain-cash-843700-300x244.jpg" alt="" width="317" height="258" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/bitcoin-blockchain-cash-843700-300x244.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/08/bitcoin-blockchain-cash-843700-768x624.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/08/bitcoin-blockchain-cash-843700-1024x832.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 317px) 100vw, 317px" /></p>
<p>Bitcoin, Ripple, Ethereum and countless others. There are more than 1600+ cryptocurrencies currently. It is hard to believe that 10 years ago they didn&#8217;t even exist. Yet in 10 years, they have reached staggering heights in terms of value. What are these new type of currencies? How is it going to affect us? Will I be rich anytime sooner?</p>
<h3>What are cryptocurrencies?</h3>
<p><strong>The Cryptocurrency</strong> is a form of digital payment system which relies on <strong>blockchain</strong> for its functioning. We all have the idea of the current currency systems like dollars, yen, rupees, roubles, etc. which relies on a central monitoring system controlled by the government. All your money is controlled by your government. Cryptocurrency takes an opposite approach.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-21" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/blockchain-3019120_1920-300x225.png" alt="" width="300" height="225" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/blockchain-3019120_1920-300x225.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/08/blockchain-3019120_1920-768x576.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/08/blockchain-3019120_1920-1024x767.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p>It relies on decentralization of blockchain technology. Rather than a central monitoring system, a very large group of computers stores information regarding your money. These computers may be located anywhere in the world, hence a single government can&#8217;t control the money.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3><strong>Why are people loving cryptocurrencies?</strong></h3>
<ul>
<li>It is fast. Have you ever sent money abroad? The best systems today take a day or few to transfer money abroad. With cryptocurrency, this is not the case. Some cryptocurrencies like Ripple take less than 5 minutes.</li>
<li>It is Fraudless. There is currently no way to counterfeit cryptocurrencies. All the information regarding every single cryptocurrency ever generated is stored in their blockchain.</li>
<li>Low settlement fees. You may be aware that when you transfer your money to some other person, the bank takes a part of it in form of overhead fees. This fee is sometimes quite noticeable and you feel like getting robbed helplessly by banks. With cryptocurrencies, this is less of an issue.</li>
</ul>
<p>A lot of institutes/companies have started integrating the new form of digital currency in their system like Starbucks, Paypal, Microsoft, etc.</p>
<h3><strong>Want to get rich with cryptocurrencies?</strong></h3>
<p><img class="wp-image-24 alignleft" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/stock-1863880_1920-300x200.jpg" alt="" width="362" height="241" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/stock-1863880_1920-300x200.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/08/stock-1863880_1920-768x512.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/08/stock-1863880_1920-1024x683.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 362px) 100vw, 362px" /></p>
<p>You can also get rich with cryptocurrencies. You can mine cryptocurrencies yourself or much better, invest in them. Though this is quite risky and even experienced traders cannot get the feel of crypto-market. If you see yourself, walking down this path, remember to research deeply on the currency you are investing on and keep yourself updated with the latest information as any disrupting news can change the prices of cryptocurrencies in minutes.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>To sum up, a lot of things are going to be changed. You may have already seen the way mobile phones have changed our everyday&#8217;s life with more yet to come. Cryptocurrencies will have the same effect in that scale. Believe it or not, but it will be a standard in a few years to trade in cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Stay tuned to know more!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptocurrencies-information-page/">What is cryptocurrency? Get rich with cryptocurrencies.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="">googlecoincrypto</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
